

# TUNAR ALYARZADA

Full Stack Developer (FE-heavy)

# **PROFILE**

Full name: Tunar Əlyarzadə

Date of birth: 05.01.1998

Place of birth: Baku, Azerbaijan

Phone: (055) 664-30-64 / (050) 611-33-15 E-mail: tunar.alyarzada.98@gmail.com

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

**Lider Advertising MMC** 

React Developer Nov 2023- April 2024

**Lider Advertising MMC** 

Intern React Developer Aug 2023- Nov 2021

#### **EDUCATION HISTORY**

Masters degree

Baku Business University Sep 2019- June 2021

**Bachelor degree** 

Azerbaijan State Economic University Jan 2015- Sep 2019

#### **PORTFOLIO**

Github: https://github.com/alyarzada

#### **ABOUT ME**

It has been around 3 years since I started developing myself in the field of front-end, and I have gained sufficient theoretical and practical knowledge. As someone who is very enthusiastic about learning new things, I have learned the latest and modern technologies in this field and added them to my skills. Over these years, in addition to small and medium-sized projects, I have developed more complex internal management systems with structured and rich content, such as "dashboards" (along with API), and gained extensive experience in front-end. In addition to this, I have been learning and have reached a certain level of proficiency in the technologies related to back-end.

# **FRONT-END TECHS**

HTML 5	
CSS 3 / SASS	
Tailwind CSS / UnoCSS	
Material UI / Ant Design	
JavaScript / TypeScript	
React js / Next js v13	
Redux Toolkit, Zustand	
AsyncThunk / RTK query	
SWR, TanStack Query	
Fetch API / Axios	
Git / GitHub	
Third-party libraries	

## **BACK-END TECHS**

Node js / Express js	
Next js v13 / Next-Auth	
Prisma ORM / Mongoose	
PostgreSQL / MongoDB	
REST API / GraphQL	
Firebase / Socket.IO	
Strapi for CMS	

## LANGUAGE SKILLS

English Russian